[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":579826,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":585622,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure t hat when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":7201,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":592827,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":17321,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":610152,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":2034,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":612190,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":7619,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":619812,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1614,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":621428,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get you r result .)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":9093,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":630523,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1423,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":631948,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4801,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":636750,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 =  2 becau se 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1476,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":638230,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3186,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":641421,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1331,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":642757,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with th e first  number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3039,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":645797,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1372,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":647172,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":3758,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":650932,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1364,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":652300,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3409,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":655710,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1314,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":657028,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3226,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":660255,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1252,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":661508,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, y ou subtr act 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3039,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":664549,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1229,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":665781,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":15419,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":681205,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":43434,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":724643,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":7151,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":731795,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2183,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":733980,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3948,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":737931,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1599,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":739531,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the  inverse  of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2929,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":742461,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2029,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":744494,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":3117,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":747612,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1303,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":748917,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":2482,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":751403,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":5414,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":756819,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":4641,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":761461,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /> <br /> H owever, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":24267,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":785731,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":9422,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":795156,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":1723,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":796884,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.1 0-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2556,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":799443,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":1663,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":801108,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<s ub>6</su b>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2417,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":803531,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1581,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":805115,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":3046,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":808163,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1287,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":809452,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately a s possib le.","rt":12966,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":822421,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3967,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":826392,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1249,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":827644,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3495,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":831140,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2885,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":834027,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3103,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":837132,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3064,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":840198,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3393,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":843595,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2928,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":846526,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3, 8 plus 4 is 12, which is over 9, so I subtract 9","response_history":["3, 8 plus 1 ","3, 8 plus 1","3, 8 plus 4 is 12m ","3, 8 plus 4 is 12m","3, 8 plus 4 is 12, which is owe ","3, 8 plus 4 is 12, which is owe","3, 8 plus 4 is 12, which is oww","3, 8 plus 4 is 12, which is ower 9, ","3, 8 plus 4 is 12, which is ower 9,","3, 8 plus 4 is 12, which is ower 9","3, 8 plus 4 is 12, which is ower ","3, 8 plus 4 is 12, which is ower","3, 8 plus 4 is 12, which is owe","3, 8 plu s 4 is 1 2, which is ow","3, 8 plus 4 is 12, which is over 9, so i","3, 8 plus 4 is 12, which is over 9, so I subgf","3, 8 plus 4 is 12, which is over 9, so I subg","3, 8 plus 4 is 12, which is over 9, so I subtract 9"],"rt":41476,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":888005,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"I'm not sure","response_history":["I'm not sure"],"rt":17190,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":905196,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":4881,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":910078,"internal_chunk_id":" 0-0.12-0 "},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":2574,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":912653,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":8815,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":921469,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6, the inverse adds to 9, except when it's 0, so the inverse of 3 has to be 6","response_history":["6, the inverse adds to 9, except when it's 0, so the inverse of 3 has to be 6"],"rt":25699,"trial_type":"q uestion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":947172,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no, because it can't make the odd numbers","response_history":["no, because it cant","no, because it can't make the odd numbers"],"rt":22407,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":969580,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no, it can't make 5 or 7 or or 8","response_history":["no, it can't make 5 or 7 ie 8","no, it can't make 5 or 7 oie 8","no, it can't make 5 or 7 or ie 8","no, it can't make 5 or 7 or 8ie 8","no, it can't make 5 or 7 or 8","no, it can't make 5 or 7 or or 8"],"rt":52455,"trial_type":" question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1022037,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no, it can't make 3 or 7 or 8","response_history":["no, it can't make 3 or 7 or 8"],"rt":17707,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1039748,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no, it can't make odd numbers","response_history":["no, it can't make odd numbers"],"rt":14033,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1053782,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be a ny posti ve counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":16558,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1070341,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1 under +n = +n minus 1","response_history":["1 under +n = +m minua 1","1 under +n = +m minus 1","1 under +n = +n minus 1"],"rt":51270,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1121613,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x ","response":"x under +n = +n minus x","response_history":["x under +n = +n minus x"],"rt":27982,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1149597,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I don't know how to find a pattern like that.  I don't see anything obvious.","response_history":["I don't know how to find a pattern like that.  I don't see anything obvious."],"rt":21862,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1171460,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":7439,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1178901,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":6188,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1185091,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":10166,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1195259,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<su b>n</sub >, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"I don't think this is true, I don't think the value of x is linked in any way as a divisor to +n.","response_history":["I don't think this is true, I don't think the value of x corrolates to N ","I don't think this is true, I don't think the value of x corrolates to N","I don't think this is true, I don't think the value of x corrolates to n as","I don't think this is true, I don't think the value of x corolates to n","I don't think this is true, I don't think the value of x c","I don't think this is true, I don't think the value of x is linked in any way as a divisor to x.","I don't think this is true, I don't think the value of x is linked in any way as a divisor to +.","I don't think this is true, I don't think the value of x is linked in any way as a divisor to +n."],"rt":81142,"trial_type":"que stion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1276404,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":119757,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1396163,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"I'm not sure of the correct answer, but I think it is sometimes because while rules in math stay the same, meaning they apply the same to each number, not every number reacts t he same  way.  I don't think it is an always or never type of situation.","response_history":["I'm not sure of the correct answer, but I think it is sometimes becaue ","I'm not sure of the correct answer, but I think it is sometimes becaue","I'm not sure of the correct answer, but I think it is sometimes because while rules in math stay the same, iffee","I'm not sure of the correct answer, but I think it is sometimes because while rules in math stay the same, iffe","I'm not sure of the correct answer, but I think it is sometimes because while rules in math stay the same, iff","I'm not sure of the correct answer, but I think it is sometimes because while rules in math stay the same, if","I'm not sure of the correct answer, but I think it is sometimes because while rules in math stay the same, i","I'm not sure of the correct answer, but I think it is sometimes because while rules in math stay the same, different numbers don't ","I'm not sure of the correct answer, but I think it is som etimes b ecause while rules in math stay the same, di","I'm not sure of the correct answer, but I think it is sometimes because while rules in math stay the same, d","I'm not sure of the correct answer, but I think it is sometimes because while rules in math stay the same, meaning they apply the same to each number, not every number reacts tha","I'm not sure of the correct answer, but I think it is sometimes because while rules in math stay the same, meaning they apply the same to each number, not every number reacts the same way.  I don't think it is an always or never type of situation."],"rt":80289,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1476455,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Somet imes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":7908,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1484365,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":1868,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1486236,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"55","response_history":["55"],"rt":2638,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1488875,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"High school diploma","response_history":["High school diploma"],"rt":3070,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1491947,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Algebra I - high school many, many years ago","response_history":["Algr","Algebra I - high school many, many years ago"],"rt":17937,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1509886,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understan d it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":5254,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1515142,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":4228,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1519372,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2  - somewhat"],"rt":5141,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1524515,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":5015,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1529533,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":5980,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1535517,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","response_history":["Female"],"rt":2525,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1538044,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":6169,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1544215,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","response_history":["no"],"rt":4642,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":1548860,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Even though  I strug gled, I enjoyed this hit.  I am not a math person by any stretch, but I am always interested in trying to learn something new.  I didn't get it entirely, but I felt like I used my brain today!","response_history":["Even though I struggled, I enjoyed this hit.  I am not a math eper","Even though I struggled, I enjoyed this hit.  I am not a math epe","Even though I struggled, I enjoyed this hit.  I am not a math ep","Even though I struggled, I enjoyed this hit.  I am not a math e","Even though I struggled, I enjoyed this hit.  I am not a math person by s","Even though I struggled, I enjoyed this hit.  I am not a math person by any stretch, though I have a child who is majoring in m","Even though I struggled, I enjoyed this hit.  I am not a math person by any stretch, though I have a child who is majoring in engo","Even though I struggled, I enjoyed this hit.  I am not a math person by any stretch, though I have a child who is majoring in engineering nan","Even though I struggl ed, I en joyed this hit.  I am not a math person by any stretch, though I have a child who is majoring in engineering na","Even though I struggled, I enjoyed this hit.  I am not a math person by any stretch, though I have a child who is majoring in engineering na","Even though I struggled, I enjoyed this hit.  I am not a math person by any stretch, though I have a child who is majoring in engineering n","Even though I struggled, I enjoyed this hit.  I am not a math person by any stretch, though I have a child who is majoring in engineering and ta","Even though I struggled, I enjoyed this hit.  I am not a math person by any stretch, though I have a child who is m","Even though I struggled, I enjoyed this hit.  I am not a math person by any stretch, though I have a child who is has","Even though I struggled, I enjoyed this hit.  I am not a math person by any stretch, though I have a child who is ha","Even though I struggled, I enjoyed this hit.  I am not a math person by any stretch, t hough I  have a child who is h","Even though I struggled, I enjoyed this hit.  I am not a math person by any stretch, tho","Even though I struggled, I enjoyed this hit.  I am not a math person by any stretch, th","Even though I struggled, I enjoyed this hit.  I am not a math person by any stretch, t","Even though I struggled, I enjoyed this hit.  I am not a math person by any stretch, but I am always interested in trying to learn something new.  I didn't get it entirely, ut ","Even though I struggled, I enjoyed this hit.  I am not a math person by any stretch, but I am always interested in trying to learn something new.  I didn't get it entirely, ut","Even though I struggled, I enjoyed this hit.  I am not a math person by any stretch, but I am always interested in trying to learn something new.  I didn't get it entirely, u","Even though I struggled, I enjoyed this hit.  I am not a math person by any stretch, but I am always interested in trying to learn something new.  I didn't get i t entire ly, but I felt like I used my brain today!"],"rt":76607,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":1625469,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]